photobiz.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy | PhotoBiz

PhotoBiz® Privacy Policy   
Effective June 3, 2014

PhotoBiz respects your right to privacy and has taken steps to secure your personal and financial information.  This Privacy Policy describes PhotoBiz's privacy practices.  We will only use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (referred to as "this Policy").  We encourage you to read this Policy to understand the types of personal information we collect and how the information is used.  This Policy is subject to change from time to time.  Please email  [privacy@photobiz.com ](mailto:privacy@photobiz.com) if you have any questions or concerns.

PhotoBiz is the sole owner of any information collected on our site or for subscription registration purposes, including customer and billing contact information.  Usernames, passwords, and IP ranges collected for the purpose of site access authentication are held in the strictest confidence.   _We will not sell, share, or distribute this information in any way, or use it for any other purpose than for site access authentication to photobiz.com and photobizcommunity.com._

The PhotoBiz Community (www.photobizcommunity.com) is an online forum sponsored by PhotoBiz.  You may opt out at any time by emailing [optout@photobizcommunity.com](mailto:optout@photobizcommunity.com).

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Cookies are required for certain parts of the PhotoBiz website to function correctly.  We and Google also use cookies for Google AdWords Remarketing, which you may opt out of (see below).

Google AdWords Remarketing

We use Google AdWords remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on our website(s).  This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future, including PhotoBiz advertising.  If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future, you can opt out using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Links 

The PhotoBiz website contains links to other sites.  Please be aware that PhotoBiz is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site.  This Policy applies solely to information collected by the PhotoBiz website. 

Email Solicitation

As a user or customer you will occasionally receive email updates from us about important functionality changes, special offers from us, new services, and other noteworthy news items about us.  We hope you will find these updates useful and informative.  If you do not want to receive promotional emails from us, simply respond to the instructions at the bottom of the email to have your email address removed from our mailing list.  PhotoBiz reserves the right to limit registration to those who will accept emails and to those who will provide the requested information.

The Security Measures We Take To Protect Your Personal Information

All credit card information is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a widely used coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt or scramble data before you send it to us.  Our website is PCI (Purchase Card Industry) compliant, as verified by an independent third-party.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. 

The Personal Information We Collect

PhotoBiz collects personal information necessary to respond to your requests for our customized products and services and to allow you to use the resources available on our website, including the creation and maintenance of a photo gallery, wedding account, and/or a wedding website.  Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, email address, and phone number.  PhotoBiz may also collect information related to your wedding, including dates and places of the rehearsal, rehearsal dinner, wedding and reception; name, address and phone number of wedding guests; information relating to your gift registry and honeymoon.  PhotoBiz also uses order forms for you to sign up for products and services.  On such order forms, we collect your contact information, financial information (including credit card numbers), and demographic information.  We also keep track of your visits to the site and all purchases you make through us with this information.

With Whom Your Information Is Shared and How It Is Used

When you provide information to PhotoBiz, the information is stored in our databases and such information is passed onto the partner photographer or vendors who are responsible for fulfilling photo orders to your event.  PhotoBiz reserves the right to contact you about your account at any time.  Information we collect is used to tailor your experience at our site, to show you content that we think you might be interested in, and to display the content according to your preferences.  We also use such personal information to send you information and promotional materials regarding our service.  Your contact information may also be used if it becomes necessary to contact you.

We may share your personally identifiable information with those companies that assist us in providing PhotoBiz service to you, known as third party service providers.  We outsource all domain & hosting companies which need information.  We also may share personally identifiable information (not including credit card information) with third parties that assist us with the administration or fulfillment of photo ordering.

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable, including (without limitation) when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.
